I can imagine you singing on Eurostar one day.
All those screaming girls wishing you could sing just for them.
You have such a beautiful voice.
You can't keep it a secret.
Why not? You keep secrets.
I do?
You said I couldn't talk about the doctor we went to.
That's true.
You mustn't.
Especially to your father.
It's our secret, okay?
Please. Okay.
Stop teaching my son to sing like a fucking queer.
Anton, it's for school.
Nobody tells me how to raise my son.
- Don't touch her! - You love your mother, huh?
You love her more than your father?
You won't love her so much...
when you know our little secret.
You're drunk.
You want to know who your mama is, huh?
- Mama's boy? - Stop it!
Stop it!
That's my boy!
I knew there was a man in there. A man like me.
I know what I am.
And I know what that makes you.
And this cunt, she's more than your mother.
No!
We have to go.
He'll find us.
I'm going to fix--
Fix it.
This time, he's not coming after us.
We're getting out of here.
Wolfgang... it's not worth it.
I'm not worth it.
Wolfgang.
Can you hear me?
Thank God.
Oh, thank God.
Don't say anything. They're monitoring everything. Okay?
Just follow me. Follow my voice.
I have you. I have you.
Do you know we have Whispers?
We're going to use him to get you free. Okay?
Don't.
What?
Because I'm-- I'm not worth it.
Wolfgang, you are.
You are.
I know what love is because of you.
I love you, Wolfgang.
And I swear we're going to get you free.
What happened? Was that Wolfgang?
They have him on sedatives and on blockers
so it was difficult to connect,
but at least they aren't hurting him anymore.
That's good.
Will said they wouldn't as long as we have Whispers.
I don't know how much longer I can wait until the exchange.
I know.
It'll be soon.
But right now, we need more of the liquid blocker.
Yes, of course.
I'm running low on methatactogen trioxide.
Nomi will have to forge another prescription.
Already on it.
It's cooked.
This should last us through the week.
I don't think we have a week. We have to go soon.
How was the d'Orsay?
Sadly, it didn't work out.
- So right now, Will is talking to Riley? - And with Sun, Kala.
Our exchange plan is based on finding the right location
and disguisable transportation,
and right now we have neither.
Yeah, we go check it out!
And now Capheus.
Capheus? But I thought he was trying to buy a police van?
Guess what I found?
The van that should work.
Great.
A little paint.
It'll be perfect.
Okay.
It's a start.
Will, what just happened?
Capheus found a van.
So, Will just saw through Capheus' eyes?
Sort of. It feels more like you're there
than you're looking through their eyes.
That is so freaking cool!
I don't know if I'll get over it. It's mind-blowing.
I can feel my ideas of self... expanding.
Sometimes it's not great.
You know we can hear you... even when you lower your voice.
I didn't mean anything.
- Who's that? - It's Nomi.
Maybe Sans Jour is the best option?
People know you've played there.
They might be expecting it after Amsterdam,
but we are running out of options.
I need Whisper's shot.
Kala.
It's ready.
And...
I'm on my way.
Wait for me.
Is there anything else on Jonas' phone?
Nothing. The only calls he made
were to the Secretary, Peapod, and Just Eat.
We need more on the Secretary.
Right now, he's our only direct line to the Chairman.
If we had better equipment...
Still no word from Bug?
No, but you know that's Bug.
Actually, it isn't like Bug at all,
but I don't want Neets to know
that I am completely freaking out about it.
BPO doesn't know he exists.
Diego couldn't find the official documents on him anywhere.
He's like a character from one of my movies.
No, he's better.
Because he's real.
We have to stay focused.
We know BPO's going to do everything they can to stop us,
but as long as we stick to our plan--
Holy shit! Now this is something.
- What? - Elizabeth.
- Who's Elizabeth? - Whisper's wife.
I thought BPO moved her and their daughter to a safe house?
There's no address listed.
But it is good to know that even people under BPO's protection
follow the same rules as the rest of us.
When they file for divorce.
Morning, Milt. On the stool.
Look at my wall.
How are you doing today?
I know you don't want to answer my questions.
You don't have to.
Jonas pretty much told me everything I need to know.
Yeah, we were just talking about you and your wife...
Elizabeth.
And Jonas really seemed to think that she loves you, but...
I don't know.
We were also talking about... your daughter.
What was her name?
Do you miss her?
A typical father would, but...
you're not typical, are you?
See, I figure when someone cuts open the skull
of a young girl like Sara Patrell while she's still alive...
they can't possibly look at another little girl
and not think about that.
Maybe you can.
As a boy, I was an exceptional student.
I loved reading.
I opened a book and found secrets and knowledge hidden inside.
When I was a medical student,
I learned how to operate on human beings.
I imagined they had names and lives,
but as far as I was concerned,
they were the same as books...
except I opened them with my knife.
Every moment I remain here brings me closer to the moment
I will open Ms. Gunnarsdottir while she is still alive
so that you can feel as I slice into her cerebellum...
and cut after cut, her secrets and knowledge
will spill across my table.
When all that remains of her and you and your cluster...
are the measurements and observations in my notebook,
I will go home...
and I will kiss my beautiful wife and my daughter...
and I will return to my exceptional life.
I wouldn't be so sure about that, Milt.
That beautiful wife of yours?
She just filed for divorce.
There's no going back.
Not for you,
not for me...
not for any of us.
That time again, Jonas.
"The bonds that bind another person
to ourself exist only in our mind."
I wonder if Monsieur Proust was a sensate.
I doubt he was ever handcuffed to a radiator.
Here you go.
I must compliment you on these blockers.
Really top-shelf stuff.
None of the nausea you get with regular homemade.
Thank you.
Still don't trust me?
Give us a reason to trust you. Tell us about the Chairman.
Now that sounds like Will talking.
If he was using you as a watchdog...
You must have talked to him.
I explained he uses a voice modulator. He wears a bio-mask.
He's quite a paranoid fellow.
- So you say. - So you say.
- Thing is, we want to trust you, Jonas. - You helped us once.
What we can't figure out is why you stopped.
It seems we keep returning
to that moment you and I first met, Will,
in the convenience store.
I asked you to choose between what you heard and what you felt.
You told me the choice you made was a mistake.
No, the mistake is thinking we're back in the same place.
We're not.
You're a prisoner handcuffed to a radiator.
So I am.
Let's talk about Angelica.
I'm trying to understand her decision to go to Chicago.
She was there looking for her first cluster.
And then she starts working with Kolovi and Whispers.
And this is the part that bothers me.
She helped build a machine
that uses lobotomized sensates to murder people.
That does not sound like the Angelica
you described in the train station.
In the ninth century,
Chinese alchemists were searching for an elixir to prolong life.
They combined saltpeter, sulfur, and charcoal...
and gave the world gunpowder.
Come on, Jonas, stop bullshitting.
Angelica.
There is no one in the world I have known better.
But I never could have imagined
what she would do during her brief life.
She left the cabin because she loved Raoul,
and somehow she could feel he was alive in Chicago.
Once she was there...
she wanted to understand what Kolovi and Whispers were doing.
She needed them to trust her.
Very soon, she realized she could use their technology
to build a machine to trace
her psycellium connection to her children.
She worked secretly,
developing a graft of neural-morphic ligature
and using the conductivity of psycellium to send a signal.
Imagine a sonar that emits not sound...
but pain.
Pain, Will.
Pain connects us.
Pain binds us better to one another than anything else.
Oh, my baby. I'm so...
Milton.
I--
I thought that you were going to laugh at me.
I just... didn't really want to show you until I was certain,
but now I am, I...
Look. It's a breakthrough.
I just followed your research.
Extraordinary.
A Chicago cop can understand that life doesn't always allow us
to be the best version of ourselves.
Particularly when circumstances demand
we lie and betray our friends...
or compels us to handcuff an ally to a radiator.
Neets?
There you are.
I couldn't sleep.
Are you okay?
Sometimes all this... it's hard.
I mean, we're in Paris, Nom.
That's the Eiffel Tower.
When I was in college,
all I thought about was coming to this city.
I was gonna live in an attic apartment
and work at Shakespeare and Co. while I wrote my novel.
I had fantasies about falling in love
with a tragically detached French girl
that I would finally break through to
when I kissed her in front of the tourists up there...
at the top of the Eiffel Tower.
You never told me any of that.
You had your past lives. I had mine too.
I got through some very tough times thinking about this city.
And now that I'm actually here
with the woman I love...
And the Eiffel Tower is right there, but we can't enjoy it
because at any moment something terrible could happen.
Listen to me, Amanita Caplan.
When I put this ring on your finger, I made you a promise,
and I am going to keep that promise.
I'm going to marry you.
I can't believe in a future where that doesn't happen,
because a future where we can't enjoy the Eiffel Tower
and kiss in front of the tourists... is no future at all.
And as impossible as that future might seem right now,
I will remind you, as you reminded me,
impossibility is still just a kiss away from reality.
I love you.
Again?
Actors.
Look, what I'm trying to explain is that...
this is an important part of his process.
Oh, he will be there.
You have a signal?
Dani, what did he say? What did he say?
What? Am I fired? Am I fired? Fired?
Is that better?
Yes. I can see you.
I can see you too.
Even pixilated, you are beautiful.
We've all been so worried.
You should be worried. I am driving the Van Damn.
- The rally worked. - Yes.
The poll numbers are rising, but the people need to see you.
Mandiba is asking,
"Who is this champion? Why is he hiding?"
Look, I promise. I will explain everything soon.
This is a problem, okay? This is a huge problem.
BPO contacted my family.
My father left a very cryptic,
confusing e-mail as if everything was all right,
which my father would never, given these circumstances.
We knew this could happen.
Nomi can check if it's serious.
Nomi's not doing anything
until Nomi has a fucking cup of coffee.
No, no, no. No, no, no, no, no.
I can't believe this is happening to us.
Why me? What's going on?
You're supposed to be running a huge election!
You're supposed to get married.
I have the biggest break of my life,
but we're trapped here!
Trapped! We're trapped here!
- Trapped! - Everybody freeze!
Okay, we all need to take a deep breath.
Okay.
I know we're all trying
to hold onto things that matter to us, but...
Wolfgang needs us.
And this is war.
Stop it!
You love your mother?
You love her more than your father?
You want to know who your mama is, huh? Mama's boy?
Stop it!
When you know our little secret...
Why Wolfgang?
Why?
You know our little secret...
You always knew.
But still, you did nothing.
My father... was a monster.
And so are you.
This cunt. She's more than your mother.
She...
She's your sister!
He married my mother.
She thought he was going to protect us.
One day, he came into my room...
I tried to run away.
He found me.
He always found me.
We have to go.
He'll find us.
I'm going to fix it.
I'll get you out of here.
How can a child be this brave?
Wolfgang, it's not worth it.
I'm not worth it.
Yes, you are.
You are my mom.
Don't shoot! We need him alive!
Move, move.
What is the point of this, Mr. Bogdanow?
We have arranged an exchange with your cluster.
There's nowhere to go from here except home.
I have no home.
No!
You can't do this.
One bullet ends all this shit.
Me and Whispers.
And me.
No!
You can't give up.
Not you.
Not now.
We knew they wanted Whispers back,
but last night proved just how badly they need him.
If I were to guess, I'd say the zombie program--
Has just one pilot.
Whispers.
But from what we know, something does not add up.
If I were an evil chairman offering an assassin-for-hire program,
I'd want more than one pilot.
You'd want a bunch of them.
And you'd want more than one neural interface thingy.
You'd want enough so that losing one wouldn't matter.
Exactly.
Dani.
You can leave it there, thank you.
Someone has to sign for it.
Bug?
Angels!
Are we happy to see you!
Oh, my!
- You've multiplied. - Yeah.
Are these all the voices?
Yeah.
What's up, Born Free?
And you know Lito.
We met in the Castro.
You remembered.
We were worried sick about you.
Sorry.
Typhoon over Bangkok held me up.
You flew to Paris from San Francisco via Thailand?
You warned me, so I was vigilant.
Took the long way around.
Then I had to chase down some
equipment via a rendez-vous avec Madame Virtuelle.
You speak French as well?
Last time, the language of love was Spanish.
Where's Sun?
There's a report from Seoul.
Just when the Bak Investments story
could not get anymore like a Hollywood movie,
Minister Tae Park has been arrested for obstruction of justice.
Tae was under investigation for his ties to Joong-Ki Bak...
I hate that guy.
But I'm kind of glad you didn't stick that rebar through him.
...and the shooting of police
detective Mun during the Bak Gala three weeks ago.
Detective Mun is said to
be making a full recovery from his injury.
Many in the media are calling the Bak Investments scandal
the story of the decade.
You could call him.
Bug brought a whole box of fresh burners.
Shit.
Hello, Detective.
Remember me?
Yeah, I think so.
You look a lot like this woman who kicked my ass a couple times.
I was trying to get her to trust me
when I got shot arresting her scumbag brother.
Thank you.
I think those two words might have made getting shot worth it.
How are you?
Good.
See?
Already back to work.
You?
Good.
Where are you?
I'm here.
That's all you need to know.
You're not here.
I wish you were.
Are you saying you miss me, Detective Mun?
As a matter of fact, Ms. Bak, that's exactly what I am saying.
Say it again.
Say what?
Say it.
I miss you like I've never missed anyone in my life.
Now you.
I miss you.
One more time.
- I have to go. - Ms. Bak. Ms. Bak?
I can't.
I've been staring at this
screen so long even my glasses are sore.
Tell me about it.
- Well, we're getting close. - We are?
After Raoul died in the cabin,
Angelica and Whispers developed the Traceworks
into what is now the drone program.
Sometime around here, they went to London together
just as Croome cut short his holiday in Zurich.
Now I'm guessing this was when Whispers demonstrated
the viability of drone technology
to the people inside BPO, including the Chairman.
But something happened, something Jonas won't talk about,
and we know that it's serious
because immediately after that trip,
the first terrorist warrants for Jonas were issued.
How does he do that?
Guys, have you seen Hernando and Dani?
They went with Amanita for croissants.
Croissants?
No. I need protein.
No sugar, no starch. No more carbs in the house, please.
No more carbs in the house! I'll eat them all!
Oh, my God.
Will, I am staying calm. I am definitely not panicking,
but I have just received a very, very worrying e-mail.
Rajan!
What are you doing here?
Oh, my God.
Rajan! What are you doing here?
My love! I had not heard from you.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I sent an e-mail.
I was worried!
These people came asking for you from some medical organization.
What organization?
But the name, I just remember three letters. BP--
Oh, shit!
Everybody move!
Grab your bag. Come on. Quick.
Come on.
Come on!
Time for one of those hard decisions, Jonas.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Kala.
Who are these people? Have you joined some insane cult?
Rajan, if I'm caught by those men back there,
they will kill me. Come on.
I don't know about you, I am not good with heights.
Kind of glad we didn't have breakfast yet.
Croissants!
Wha-- Did I leave the door open?
Hernando. Dani.
Freeze! Hands in the air!
Oh, shit!
Shit? What shit?
- Nomi! - Amanita's in trouble.
Family, we're coming!
Nomi!
Jonas!
I'm on your side.
Fuck!
Amanita!
Get down! Freeze!
Freeze!
Freeze.
Freeze! Knees on the floor.
Don't shoot.
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
Nom!
Hot damn! I have been waiting to see that!
Are you okay? I thought we lost you.
Shit!
We should secure these men,
clear anything we need, and get back to the squat.
I'm not going anywhere until someone tells me
just what in the hell is going on here!
Come with me.
I'm not sure what I am supposed to say
if what I've just heard is true.
Rajan, I know it's not an easy thing, okay?
It took me a long time myself to accept that--
That you are... A different type of human being to me.
Yes.
That you are telepathically connected to seven other people.
Telepathy's not exactly...
But basically, yes.
And here I thought I was the one with the big secrets.
I didn't know how to tell you.
Or anyone.
And this was all happening to you before our wedding?
Yes.
Little wonder you were so confused.
And in... Positano?
Yes!
So, when this Wolfgang fellow is tortured,
you experience his pain?
That sounds terrible.
Look...
I know this is all a shock
and that it might be best for you
to take some time away and just--
But you are in danger now, Kala.
So you believe me?
Would you, could you concoct a lie of this extraordinary magnitude?
No.
Are you and all of these people out there medically insane?
I don't think so.
So what other choice do I have?
I came rushing to Paris for the same reason I married you.
I love you, Kala.
And that feeling hasn't gone away or been changed
by learning that the woman I love...
is so much more than the woman I married.
My God, Rajan.
I married a good man.
Sans Jour is down there, next to the river.
It's close to the metro. That's good for us.
Georges said there's a back entrance we could use
and they could bring in extra security.
These club owners are really into you, aren't they?
Oh, how I've missed you.
As beautiful as ever.
This is Will,
the one I told you about.
My rival. Very well.
Shall we say pistols at dawn?
English only, I imagine.
French if you prefer.
And pistols suit me just fucking fine.
I like him already.
Come.
- You know French? - No, but you do.
I have a certain understanding with the local police.
It's not the local police we're worried about.
Vincent told me these men threatened to close his club down.
We've had many kinds of people threaten us in Paris...
attack us and our way of life.
Our answer has been and will always be the same.
Vive la résistance.
Or like you say in English, "Fuck off."
Give me that.
If Will is right and
Angelica and Whispers came to London together...
whatever happened there could explain the rift
that shunted Kolovi out of the picture.
Right.
Blocker time.
Right. Just a moment, let me get the shot ready.
You were right.
Georges is one of a kind.
So how close were you two?
You know... close.
Okay, my bad cop feeling about this is buzzing.
What?
Someone's following us.
Shit.
- Do you have your phone? - No.
Let's go.
Ringing.
It just keeps ringing.
Nothing.
You can't visit?
They're on blockers.
What about Capheus?
What's up?
We have a problem.
You're nowhere near the squat.
- I could drive. - You'll be too late.
Whispers will be off the blockers if he isn't already.
This is not like Will. Something's wrong.
Very wrong.
In 10 minutes, Whispers will be able
to visit with anyone he's connected to.
If he knows about where we are...
I'll go.
What?
No. No way.
We talked about it. He already knows me.
I can do the shot.
I just need someone to watch my back.
Anyone know how to use this thing?
Joaquin.
My tía always said that
even assholes are useful for shitting and fucking.
Oh, Ms. Caplan.
Come to play doctors and nurses?
Is it easy for you to sound like a creepy villain
or is it something you have to work at?
On the stool. Eyes to the wall. You know the routine.
And who's the sidekick's sidekick?
Too afraid to show your Latina face?
Aren't there more convivial ways
for two pretty ladies to occupy their time in gay Paris?
Oh, you don't have to say anything.
Your desire for shopping is palpable.
Oh, did that hurt?
An engagement ring, Ms. Caplan?
Given your recent failed marriage,
I'll pass on whatever sage wisdom you were considering sharing.
Yes.
Well in due time, you too will discover
the unbridgeable differences between our species.
It's the smallness of your kind, the limits of the sapien mind
that attracts my kind.
It's akin to the way humans like to keep their pets.
Sooner rather than later,
Ms. Marks will discover that being married to you
is no different from being married to a Labrador bitch.
I never forget a face.
I see you too.
Tricky.
And I know your kind.
Men that mistake cruelty for strength.
Living your petty little lives, so limited.
We both know that if I were to pull this trigger,
not a single person would shed a tear.
The smallness of your kind of life is nothing to fear...
only to pity.
Okay, that rocked!
It was Bodhi.
From the plane?
I thought she said it was pointless to try to change the world.
That you can only change yourself.
Apparently her rules have changed.
She's not the only one changing the way the game is played.
Mr. Hoy!
- What's happening? - A purge!
As you can see, the trap snaps shut.
Come on now, Ms. Blue, before they hang, draw, and quarter me.
I've got two ladies who want words.
You may recall your fellow countrywoman.
Yrsa?
You're still alive!
I am, Riley.
For now.
Kala, what's happening?
Riley's visiting Mr. Hoy.
But she's here.
Been there.
I've been in hiding since I fled Iceland.
BPO knows that I feigned a heart attack to bring the ambulance.
It was you.
You saved my life.
If you want to thank me,
listen to the woman who urged me to help you.
Riley, I'm a sapien, so I can't see you.
My name is River El-Saadawi. You may have heard of my mother.
Of course.
I lead the faction inside BPO
still fighting to return to the original principles
as envisioned by my mother and Mr. Hoy.
Those days are long gone, and I'm afeard I'm right behind them.
Hoy.
They're attacking our people in Manchuria.
Evacuate whoever's left to Jeju Island.
Godspeed, Admiral.
You too, Speaker.
Mr. Hoy, the Queen of Naples is behind this purge.
The mendacious minx will be coming for you next, Sutra.
Let us help you.
Oh, you can help me, Ms. Blue,
by keeping your word and paying your debt to the Archipelago.
- How? - By doing what River asks you to do!
I was hoping to have this conversation in person.
I didn't think the situation could get any more dire
after Richard Croome's assassination,
but I obviously underestimated our chairman's ruthlessness.
Like you, we are now being hunted, and imprisoned or worse.
Our only hope is if...
If what?
You must kill Whispers.
By killing him, you kill the drone program
and cripple the Chairman's hold over the BPO.
I know what it will cost you,
but this is war.
What? What's going on?
It's some kind of organized attack.
BPO has found Hoy.
Ms. El-Saadawi believes that their only hope...
is if we kill Whispers.
But then they will kill Wolfgang.
I'm sorry.
We had to try.
Take your blocker, dear.
Exposure is dangerous.
Riley, I pray that one day
we'll somehow emerge from this darkness.
Thank you.
This is it.
This is the end.
Goodbye, Mr. Hoy.
Goodbye.
Where are you going?
I've-- I've nowhere left to run.
You may wish to look away.
Don't give up. Please.
Bless you, lassie, but I'm the Speaker of the Archipelago.
I can't let BPO get hold of me.
Don't say that. I got you into this.
If we hadn't met in Amsterdam, you'd still be--
Cowering in my coffin, living like a hunted rat?
Aye. I would, Ms. Blue.
But if I died there, I'd die soused in regret.
If I die here--
That's it.
Let's nip in the bud all this nonsense about dying.
- Aunt Kirsty? - Mrs. Stromness?
How did you get here?
By taxi, you great numpty.
What? But... you shouldn't be here!
It's not safe.
Well, it's a great deal safer now
since I chucked the bullets out the window.
What have you done?
Look...
I promised Angus I'd mind you.
So take a blocker.
If we're arrested, it will buy you a period of grace.
You-- You knew?
About Homo sensorium?
I was Angus' wife for 40 years.
You can't love someone like I loved Angus
and not know a thing like that.
Take your medicine.
Don't worry about me. I'll be fine.
- Go! Go! - Clear!
Freeze!
- What happened? - Did Hoy survive?
I don't know.
The connection was broken.
Now he's gone.
You're supposed to say trick or treat.
Cluster zero eight zero eight. Code FH.
F for feral, H for hostile.
And CH is for Chairman.
And also chickenshit.
I'm no more afraid of you than a doctor fears illness.
Then take off your mask.
Anonymity is a regrettable necessity of this war.
But when at last it is over,
I imagine my efforts may well remain uncredited,
which is as it should be.
My work is its own reward.
Don't worry.
I'm going to make sure you get everything you are due.
For millennia, my kind have subjugated yours.
Do you know why?
Certainty.
There is only one voice telling me what to do.
You?
You grabbed a gun
and you had the opportunity to destroy all my efforts,
but you failed.
Your kind suffer from too many conflicting thoughts,
too many clamoring voices inside your skulls.
Fortunately, I know a single, simple cure to shut them all up.
Come on.
Pull that fucking trigger.
You chicken-fucking shit! Come on! Show me your certainty!
You cockless fuck, do it!
You will leave us in the morning.
I await your swift and certain return.
You and me both.
Communication is crucial.
In The Devil Died at Dawn,
there was a hostage exchange at a club.
- It was a bullfighting stadium. - Was it?
Oh, yeah, and the bull gored you--
Guys?
Sorry.
The blocker should have metabolized by now.
Wolfgang!
Are you all right?
Hello, sexy.
No!
I told you our fates were connected.
What is she doing here?
Your cluster wanted to make sure you were undamaged
and we want the same thing.
Ms. Facchini is the only sensate
connected to both you and Milton.
Lucky me.
Ready to come home, Milton?
In order to execute the exchange,
one of us is going to have to make contact with Lila.
Since I'm already connected to Whispers,
it just makes sense that it would be me.
BPO will lock the area down straight after the exchange.
We've been monitoring local police
and BPO isn't involving them
beyond the standard terror alerts.
We think we can use that to our advantage.
Who looks more like a terrorist organization than BPO?
Officers!
- Please. - Yes, sir?
Brave chiefs of the law.
I'm listening, sir.
There is a threat right behind me.
Excuse me?
- Terrorists. - Terrorists?
They are going to attack! Protect the people!
- Don't joke. - Protect the people!
- Let's go! - Watch out!
Watch out!
Watch out! Watch out!
Get out of the car!
Hands up!
In view of our apartment evacuation,
we've relocated logistic support to a mobile response vehicle.
I can't believe I'm actually in one of those planning scenes.
- Bug. - Sorry.
It's my pleasure to report the Bugmobile is
nearly operational.
We told you we needed it now.
Did I say "nearly"?
I meant totally, absolutely ready to roll. I mean...
Yeah, that's it.
Bug!
Shit!
I mean, merde!
So once we've set the time and place,
we need as many eyes on Sans Jour as possible.
The metal detectors will help,
but we should assume they won't play by the rules.
BPO will send every cop or agent
they have as soon as they have the exchange point.
Hello.
Buy me a drink?
Sorry, honey.
Gay?
We wish.
Two at the bar are cops. Definitely cops.
Got it.
Capheus will drop us here.
We are here.
Ready.
I scouted the exit.
The van's almost ready.
Do you think we have any chance of surviving this?
I did not think I would survive prison.
I did not think I would survive the Bak Gala.
And the truth is...
I did not.
We did.
Yeah, I have a good feeling about this too.
Spirit of Jean-Claude.
We have control of street security cameras.
We're waiting to hear about ones in the club.
Georges sent the codes. You should be able to log on.
Checking them now.
There's Wolfgang.
We got Lila entering the club.
Once we have Wolfgang, we get out
and make our separate ways to the rendezvous.
In order to evacuate the club
without causing any panic or stampede,
I thought of smoke pots,
which we use at festivals.
By adding a few spices,
I was able to make the smell quite intense,
which I think will cause people--
So that proves that--
Okay. This is it.
Do you see that woman?
Keep us close to her.
Will!
It's Bodhi!
- What's happening? - I lost Whispers!
They lost him.
Fuck!
I got him.
Sorry, lover. This is goodbye.
- She's pointing a gun! - No!
Start the exit.
Everybody out of the pool.
Dani, Hernando, drop the pots.
Everyone better get out of there.
Where is Kala?
I don't know.
Lito, Dani, and Hernando have her.
They're heading for the metro.
Come on, let's go! Come on!
Make the change.
Right.
Ah, Ms. Facchini.
Milton... at last.
Exit here and go right.
Hold it.
- Is everyone out? - So far.
I've got Lito, Hernando, Dani, and Kala.
- Were you scared? - It was frightening like a movie, yes.
But it was real, which made it in a certain way--
It was the most freaking amazing experience of my life!
What about Wolfgang?
I'm good.
Where's Rajan?
He's with me. I'll meet you at the rendezvous.
All right.
Go on.
Wait. What about Sun?
Hey you! Stop!
Get on the ground! Hands on your head.
- Hands on your head! - Get down!
On your knees! Don't move!
Get her down. We'll bring her with the others.
Excuse me, officers.
But I have a warrant for that woman right there.
I don't know who you are or what language that is,
but you need to turn around and walk away.
Sorry, she's coming with me.
I said, fuck off!
Bonsoir, Ms. Bak.
What are you doing here?
Had some vacation days saved up.
Never been to Paris.
I've heard people fall in love here all the time.
Be serious. How did you find me?
In my 13 years on the force, I never committed a felony.
But regrettably, that is no longer true.
I illegally used a satellite tracking system
to find someone who was no longer wanted by the police
but who happened to call me...
with this phone.
I'll have to report you.
Of course.
Are you going to tell me
why you went to all this trouble, Detective?
I'm not really good with words, Ms. Bak.
Would you mind if I showed you instead?
Okay... I found Sun.
She's good. Like, really good.
How--
I told her to throw that phone away.
Those things are so easy to track.
Didn't she know that?
I did, so technically...
Hey, come on. What about Lila?
Right, Lila.
They're just leaving the 11th arrondissement.
I need a meeting with the Chairman immediately.
I want to personally head
the task force that hunts these animals down.
And will someone get these things off me?
In a moment, darling.
That's her.
Is that our siren?
That's not us.
Something's wrong.
Driver, what's happening?
It was Lila.
She set us up.
Now what?
Rajan. This place is amazing.
Yeah. My friend, Jean-Pierre, has owned it for years.
They'll be here soon.
Rajan...
most men wouldn't have done what you did for me.
I did what I could.
I'll never forget it.
Here they come.
Oh, Ganesha.
What do I do here?
What rules do I follow?
If I may?
Since you can, in fact,
be in more than two places at the same time,
defying several laws of physics,
I would suggest that... there are no rules.
Rajan, you are so much more than the man I thought I married.
Yeah, definitely.
Guys, how about some bubbly?
One, two, three!
Have you ever tried it yet?
To my friend Jean-Pierre!
Wait. I want to say something.
I have lived much of my life with one friend,
with my one brother.
And I never knew what it was like to...
have people in your life that would fight for someone like me.
Thank you.
You big German lug.
- We love you! - Thank you.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Even after everything we've been through...
would any of us go back to the world we're used to?
Even if that world included Milton Brandt.
Bodhi.
She's back?
She's not here, but she's in your head?
I'm confused. We've never met, but I can see you.
Me too.
There are things I can explain and things I cannot.
But before I begin, you must accept the Mother's invitation.
Who is the Mother?
I am.
Welcome.
This is the Lacuna.
You have questions.
Actually, yes. Um, to begin with, "Lacuna"?
A temple, a college, a discipline, or what precisely?
A home.
The Lacuna exists between that which is theirs or ours,
and the sensates who live here
curate a unique corpus of knowledge passed down centuries.
We are in the world, but not of the world.
You seem pretty of this world
when you sent her to follow us and kill Brandt.
One day, I believe, Bodhi will sit here.
Mother of a future Lacuna.
It is both a worry and a source of hope
that she retains a certain independence of mind.
Brandt must be destroyed.
You think Brandt is working with sapiens.
But we here in the Lacuna know his true goal.
You mean the drone assassin program.
No. Brandt is manipulating BPO.
For what?
I am a trinity of mothers.
I gave birth long ago to a girl who lived to be a mother herself.
I am the Mother of the Lacuna.
And I am the mother of my own cluster.
Only one of my eight remains.
He has many names,
but his original one is Milton Brandt.
You're Whisper's mother?
I was not then who I am now.
What mother could be unchanged
by the murder of her seven children
by the eighth?
I felt each one...
their anguish...
their terror...
Their deaths.
I tried to stop him.
Failed.
It was unbearable.
I fled from my life...
from myself...
from the world...
until I came here.
The Lacuna strikes me as very powerful.
Why wait until now to try to stop him?
Clustercide wreaks a terrible price.
My son experienced his cluster's deaths
both as murderer and murdered.
A dread of dying has poisoned his soul.
But what does that have to do with the drone program?
The zombies.
If Whispers could inhabit them with his consciousness intact...
And if he had enough of them...
Then he could live forever.
The Lacuna prizes its neutrality, but Bodhi argued...
That neutrality, in the face of such evil, is complicity.
Her view prevailed.
And the Lacuna resolved to intervene.
Can you help us find Whispers?
Mothers and children retain a connection.
There is an umbilical cord that remains uncut...
until death.
I'm still surprised you agreed to help us.
At this point, Ms. Bak,
you'll have a hard time getting rid of me.
Don't tell me you speak Italian as well.
Ma certo.
Another language of love?
For the Bug, love has no nationality.
Can you believe yesterday I thought the worst thing in my life
was being subpoenaed for a corruption trial,
and today I am heading to Naples to stop a nefarious organization
from using a secret human species,
which my wife is a member of, as suicide assassins.
What was that, Rajan?
I said... things change so fast.
Yeah. So fast!
Like driving on clouds, yeah?
Yeah, like driving on clouds.
You can hear her music?
If I want to.
Love that song.
Turn it up.
What?
No.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I can't believe you're here
and not in lots of little pieces.
Wolfie, I was worried this time.
- Glad to see you too, brother. - Yeah.
My brother, Felix!
This is Capheus.
Okay.
And you must be India Plan.
Um, I'm Kala. It's nice to finally meet.
Yeah. Good to meet you.
And I'm Rajan.
My husband.
It's complicated.
Well, let me show you something that's not complicated.
Compliments from Sebastian Fuchs.
Herr Fuchs is a firm believer in the moral necessity of revenge
and he hopes his gifts will be useful to you against,
and I'm quoting, "The Neapolitan bitch."
He included your favorite toy.
For old time's sake.
No.
What did he say?
Naples. The end of the line.
Of course.
Let me guess, this is your
"It's hopeless, Will, turn back now" speech?
I know you won't listen to me,
but if I don't say this to you, I will regret it.
We talked once of secrets.
How their world is built of and on secrets.
One way to survive inside that kind of world
is to become a secret yourself.
What secret?
The same secret I have kept
and I must continue to keep
even as I ask you to stay away from Naples.
Nice try, Jonas.
But after watching you
sip cocktails while we were being tortured,
our confidence in your ability
to finish this fight is not particularly high.
Mr. Gorski.
The man everyone underestimates.
And Wolfgang, the man everybody wants.
Welcome to my home.
I can tell you're going to keep me up at night, aren't you?
Missed you, sexy.
I don't associate happy thoughts with murder,
but I think I'm going to enjoy killing you.
You were a lot more fun when we first met.
How about you, Officer?
Are you any fun?
Me?
I'm the life of the party,
especially when Camorra queens help shadow governments
hunt down and lobotomize people I care about.
Difficult times, difficult choices.
BPO is like any government.
To deal with them, you have to speak their language:
force.
I told you this cluster would not go away.
They are too late.
But I'm pleased you came to my city.
You will witness a turning point in our struggle.
I told you I was going to build a sanctuary, Wolfgang.
And what better place than my Napoli?
Here, memories live beside history,
history beside memories.
Right there is where I had my first kiss.
And just ahead is the square
where Masaniello, a common fisherman,
stood up to the Spanish Empire and ignited a revolution
that created the first Neapolitan Republic.
Fuck that.
You're not a revolutionary. Just another collaborator.
- Stay back. - I can take him.
Not now. There is too much at stake.
This city has existed for thousands of years.
Empires and armies came and went,
and our home still stands.
Someone will survive this war.
That someone will be me.
Let's dig in. Dig in.
Oh, my God.
If I had to choose a final meal,
it would be pizza!
I spent a while here, laying in a hospital bed
and I have never eaten so well.
I was in a hospital too!
Terrible food, man.
What happened to you?
It's probably the funniest honeymoon story you've ever heard.
Rajan, right now is probably not the right time to tell them.
Oh, my God, we're in Naples.
This is amazing!
International Most Wanted!
Diego!
What's up, Iceland?
Good to see you.
You made it.
Of course I did, because if I asked you to aid and abet
who knows what felonies in foreign jurisdictions,
I'm sure you'd drop everything and race to the airport too.
So, who is, you know, human here?
Oh, no.
Hello, bowling ball.
- It's Puck. - How did he know we'd be here?
Hello, princess. Did you miss me?
Oh, my God.
What?
- Puck! - Let's go.
The Archipelago told us you were coming.
Is Mr. Hoy still alive?
I don't know.
If he is, he's on blockers.
Come on, let's go.
This vongole.
Not like the tourist shit across the street.
Andale. Let's go. Vamos.
Again with the hair?
Puck, it's creepy.
What?
I don't know what you are talking about.
So, we've had our eyes on Facchini for years.
She's part of the Palugio family.
She spent time abroad as a gun for hire in Europe
and as a sniffer for BPO.
But she always remained close to her people here.
This is Alphonse. And Sutra.
We hunt collaborators.
And Lila Facchini's cluster is one of the worst.
We've been monitoring Ms. Facchini's network for a while.
Yeah, we think she may have
smuggled the Cannibal into the Palugio rione.
But our problem is where.
There are several palazzos from which they run their business.
It's that one.
The Forcella? How do you know that?
A reliable source.
- The Forcella won't be easy. - Let's be very clear.
The Forcella is impossible.
Why is that?
The gate is off Via Becchino.
Yeah. And it's guarded. Twenty-four seven.
Even the polizia come by invitation only.
And if they don't invite you?
Camorra baptism.
That doesn't sound good.
A shower of bullets at point-blank range.
Definitely not good.
I'm sorry.
First, I have to admit
that the closest I've come to executing a military strategy
was gaining tenure at my university,
but it seems that what this plan needs...
is a Trojan horse.
I'm not really sure how that's going to help us, mate,
but... A couple of Trojans right here.
No. No, that wasn't quite what I had in mind.
It was, uh, close to this very spot
that the great poet Virgil
allegedly wrote part of his epic poem The Aeneid,
which depending on whether you are from Italy or Greece,
is a masterpiece or a knockoff.
Tourists. They're like fucking rats.
Of course, you all know that Virgil wrote,
"Amor vincit omnia!"
"Love conquers all things."
He also wrote the descent into Hell is easy,
but maybe I think I'll skip that part.
Okay, okay...
Stop the bus.
Stop it. Stop it.
Okay, phase one.
The horse is inside.
We have come in search of Virgil.
No, no, no. No, Virgil!
Isn't it incredible to breathe the air that Virgil once breathed?
Is this Italian leather?
A little bit close. Close. My wife.
We're just fine.
We have to be careful. This is when they'll be suspicious.
We're watching.
Get back on that fucking bus!
- Now! - Go. Go, go, go, go.
Phase two.
Operation Gas And Oil.
Sorry. Sorry. Okay.
Wait, please. I'm going for the hood. For the hood.
Please. Please. Okay?
Okay, wait. Okay, it's an oil problem.
Okay.
I can--
You should have said that from the start!
Just open and then...
Okay. Now we try.
Now we try, okay? No problem. Yeah.
Okay.
I have a good feeling about it this time.
Okay, let me turn the key.
Okay.
Everyone off the bus!
Off the bus!
They're here.
Keep them away from Milton.
I'm on my way.
We're coming out!
Ready.
- Phase three. - Extraction!
- Just keep thinking... Eiffel Tower! - Eiffel Tower!
You know anything about guns?
I don't, but you do.
Let's go!
I could do this every day with you, Ms. Bak.
Hurry up!
This staircase leads to the top floor.
Got it.
Was that Nomi? What's happening?
Didn't you listen?
We don't know where exactly they're holding Whispers.
- We're all covering different sections. - Yeah, but what if--
My wife...
You're a killer!
I'm sorry.
Can you teach me?
Okay, first, this isn't a real gun.
It's a Taser.
- This is a gun. - All right.
- Here's the safety. - All right.
Do not point unless you're sure about the target, okay?
Oh, shit this is serious!
You all right?
Goddamn it, Gorski.
You know I should be in fucking Pensacola, right?
Come on, let's go!
Not again!
Come! Come! Come! Come!
Will you get him to Bug?
I'll go this way.
All right.
Come. Come.
Why do I always have to get shot?
Sorry, man.
What?
Joong-Ki.
Just when I was starting to forget about him.
Lila's entering the palazzo.
Goddamn it. We need to clear this floor.
He's got to be upstairs.
Okay.
He's secure.
Good.
It's her.
Listen. Shh. Go around.
Okay.
Time to go, Milton.
What the fuck?
Ms. Bak, what is it? Look at me. Tell me.
Kala.
Kala, I love you.
Please.
Kala.
Kala! Kala.
My love. My love.
Well, is anyone gonna actually do anything?
Or are you going to just let me die in your arms?
You're alive.
- She's alive? - She's alive!
But I won't be if you don't do something quickly.
What do I do?
Save my life.
First, lay me down and stop the bleeding.
Oh, my love!
- Press it. Press that on her wound. - Oh, God.
Press it hard.
- Harder! I'm not that fragile. - Harder!
Harder.
I don't seem to have ruptured any major artery.
But I've lost blood.
She doesn't think a major artery is ruptured.
What now?
Compression to keep my blood circulating.
We should keep her blood moving. All right. Okay.
And oxygen to protect my brain.
She needs oxygen.
Her heart, it's not beating! It's not beating.
Kala.
I hear you.
Don't leave me. Stay with me.
Please! Don't stop.
Stay with me.
You said I couldn't give up.
You can't either.
Stay with me.
Wolfgang! How about this?
All right.
My wife. Kala.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
To think, I might never have kissed these lips again.
- My husband. - My wife.
You're a genius.
My love, now what do we do?
- Take her to the hospital! - Yeah. Yeah.
No, no. We have to get Lila.
Lila's gone.
We don't know where she's gonna meet the Chairman.
It could be anywhere.
Or it could be at a heliport
where they just cleared a BPO helicopter
for an emergency landing.
I got him.
You go.
The helicopter is on approach.
Shit.
Hang on, hang on. There's major military support.
Please, Jonas! Not now!
Unintentional, believe me.
But I promise this will be the last time.
"We are healed of suffering only by experiencing it to the full."
I wonder if Monsieur Proust was ever shot.
What happened?
Jonas, what are you doing?
Keeping my word.
Promise me.
You have to promise me.
So here we are. The end.
No more secrets, no more lies.
After Raoul was killed,
we learned Milton was going to meet with the Chairman
to demonstrate the viability of the drone program.
Angelica had a plan.
She smuggled two of our cluster into the facility.
Secrecy was essential.
But Harry... Poor Harry.
This isn't how we planned it.
I'm not you, Angelica.
I know.
It wasn't my idea.
You have to warn everybody.
Harry, what's going on?
Halt! Stop!
Angelica. It was her.
She tried to kill the Chairman.
This is the secret I couldn't talk about.
The psycranium.
Angelica tuned it to the psychic ligature of Whisper's brain.
He believed he alone had the power to control the drones.
He was wrong.
This was her prototype. We kept it as insurance.
Our secret.
I respect what you have done, Ms. Facchini,
but if you betray me again, I will destroy you.
I'm already on blockers, thank you.
And you have lied to me before.
All right, Ms. Facchini.
Give me Dr. Brandt and you can have your rione.
First I need the one thing
I know will ensure your ongoing cooperation.
My identity.
As we agreed, Mr. Chairman.
Oh, yes.
Your kind did this to me.
And one day--
Jonas, what just happened?
My love.
You did it.
I will always...
Be here.
Goodbye, Will.
Jonas.
Jonas!
Fuck!
What just happened?
I don't know, but I have a request from the pilot.
Shit!
We can scramble the air traffic clearance,
but it will only give us a minute.
That's all we need.
Come on, Milton.
Or do you want me to leave you for Officer Gorski?
Shit!
They're getting away.
Like hell they are.
Mr. Hoy. You're alive!
Barely, Ms. Blue.
I was just explaining to River
how Mrs. Stromness thundered through that room
laying waste to all those BPO platoons.
Aunt Kirsty?
Aye, Ms. Blue.
If it was a film...
I wouldn't have believed it.
So, how's your gunshot?
Oh, I'm feeling much better. Thank you.
We actually have a really good doctor in Italy.
Yeah. He's practically family.
- Buongiorno, my friends. - Ah, Dottore.
So, you're back again,
but this time you did not dodge the bullet.
So, have you talked with Rajan,
you know, about the future?
No.
Do you think it will work out?
I don't know.
Are you kidding me?
So the hearing went well?
Yeah, the court exonerated her of all charges.
That's great.
We would've been back sooner,
but she wanted to introduce her family to me.
Shit. That's serious. How'd that go?
Pretty good.
Well. Look at you.
Oh, my God. Leave it to Michael...
Mom, I am warning you.
Leave it to Nomi to turn what should be
a simple civil service into a spectacle.
I think it's awesome!
It's crazy I know, but
that woman over there is a special minister
in the French government and she made all of this happen.
Oh, come, come, come.
This is her.
The spirit of Jean-Claude.
Spirit of Jean-Claude.
Dad.
Sven.
This is Will.
- Come here, man. - Okay.
I'm blessed.
I know what you did for my daughter.
I'll never be able to thank you enough.
Sir, the day I met your daughter...
was the best day of my life.
You must be Janet.
I am.
I'm-- I'm Grace. I'm Amanita's mother.
And we're her dads.
I'm Tom.
We all just love Nomi so much.
What an extraordinary woman.
You must be very proud of her.
We are.
We were just talking about when they first met.
Such a great story.
I don't think we know it.
Well, Amanita used to go through girlfriends
the way people binge TV shows.
When Nomi went to City Lights...
She was looking for this obscure book...
And when she found Amanita...
When she was shelving returns.
And the book that Nomi was
looking for was right there in Amanita's hand.
Which is just about the
best description of love we've ever heard.
- That's normal, honey. - Okay.
Thank you.
You are so beautiful.
Thanks, Bug.
No, thank you for being my family.
Thank you for being mine.
You look amazing.
So do you.
Thank you.
The improbable unfolding of recent events
have led me to consider
that no one thing is one thing only.
How people endow what is familiar with
new, ever-evolving meaning and by doing so,
release us from the expected, the familiar
into something unforeseeable.
It is in this unfamiliar realm,
we find new possibilities.
It is in the unknown, we find hope.
Here we stand in the Eiffel Tower,
which was conceived in gratitude for the French Revolution.
It has been a zeppelin lookout, a transmitter tower,
and, for generations of Parisians,
an aspiration for a better, a brighter future.
Similarly plural in meaning is a wedding.
A wedding is a celebration
which can also be understood
as a union of two families...
and in this case,
this union takes on an even deeper significance.
And for me, this wedding is proof.
Proof that for all the differences between us
and all the forces that try to divide us...
they will never exceed the power of love to unite us.
Oh, God.
My love...
We live in a world that distrusts feelings.
Over and over, we are reminded that feelings
are not as important as reason.
That feelings are childish,
irresponsible, dangerous.
We are taught to ignore them, control, or deny them.
We barely understand what they are, where they come from,
or how they seem to understand us
better than we understand ourselves.
But I know that feelings matter.
Sometimes, they're little...
like when I smell cinnamon toast and I miss my grandma.
And sometimes, they are huge...
like when I found out my girlfriend shares her thoughts
with seven other people around the world.
However, if you're lucky...
I mean, really lucky...
a feeling comes along that will change everything.
I remember such a feeling and how it walloped me years ago
when this girl walked into my bookstore.
It is the same feeling that I have right now.
The feeling that this is her.
My love.
My wife.
This is my future.
And I trust this feeling
more than I have trusted anything in my life.
Thank you.
Amanita...
I wrote this thing like a hundred times
and I tore them all up
because I have to admit, I don't like vows.
I'm afraid of things pretending
to be permanent because nothing is permanent.
My life, especially these past two years,
is a testament to the fact that things change,
people change.
But with you...
that doesn't scare me.
It actually makes me happy.
It makes me excited...
because I can think of no better life
than watching Amanita Caplan change...
watching her evolve and grow.
I want to see everything that you become.
I want to know what your hair looks like in a year
and decades from now.
I may not be a tragically detached French girl,
but I want to live in an attic apartment in Paris
and bring you tea as you write your novel.
And when we're both wrinkled old ladies,
with cellulite covering my ass,
bunions all over your feet,
both of us hogging the blankets...
I know I will still remember this moment.
I will still be wearing this ring.
Because inside your arms
is the only place
I've ever felt like I was home.
Well, then, by the power invested in me,
I pronounce you wife and wife.
A gift from Paris and the new BPO
in honor of the accord and this celebration.
Thank you.
I always cry at weddings.
Me too.
Try one.
You'll never be the same again.
Have you talked to either of them?
No.
Do you know what you want?
Nomi!
I don't know what I was thinking.
Nomi...
It's a beautiful name.
Lawrence, why didn't we come to Paris until now?
What just happened?
I don't know.
As a wedding present,
we want to send you wherever you wish to go for your honeymoon.
We insist.
That is so sweet.
But--
There's only one place that we want to go.
My God.
I didn't think such things were possible.
* We're a thousand miles from comfort *
* We have traveled land and sea *
* But as long as you are with me *
* There's no place I'd rather be *
* I would wait forever *
* Exalted in the scene *
* As long as I am with you *
* My heart continues to beat *
* With every step we take *
* Kyoto to the Bay *
* Strolling so casually *
* We're different and the same Gave you another name *
* Switch up the batteries *
* If you gave me a chance I would take it *
* It's a shot in the dark But I'll make it *
* Know with all of your heart You can't shame me *
* When I am with you There's no place I'd rather be *
* No, no, no, no, no *
* No place I'd rather be *
* We staked out on a mission *
* To find our inner peace *
* Make it everlasting *
* So nothing's incomplete *
* It's easy being with you *
* Sacred simplicity *
* As long as we're together *
* There's no place I'd rather be *
* With every step we take Kyoto to the Bay *
* Strolling so casually *
* We're different and the same *
* Gave you another name *
* Switch up the batteries *
* If you gave me a chance I would take it *
* It's a shot in the dark But I'll make it *
* Know with all of your heart You can't shame me *
* When I am with you There's no place I'd rather be *
* No, no, no, no, no *
* No place I'd rather be *
* When I am with you There's no place I'd rather be *
* Be *
* Be, be, be, be, be *
* If you gave me a chance I would take it *
* It's a shot in the dark But I'll make it *
* Know with all of your heart You can't shame me *
* When I am with you There's no place I'd rather be *
* No, no, no, no, no *
* No place I'd rather be *
* When I am with you There's no place I'd rather be *